researchnowsurveys.com 2015-06-23

# Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy 

**Who are we?**

Research Now Group, Inc. (a US company), Research Now Limited (a UK company), Research Now Pty Ltd. (an Australian company), Research Now Inc. (a Canadian Company), Research Now Consulting (Shanghai) Co., Ltd. (a Chinese company), Research Now Technology Hellas EPE (a Greek Company), Research Now GmbH (a German Company), Research Now PTE Ltd. (a Singaporian Company), Research Now Pty Ltd. (a New Zealand company), Research Now Spain S.L. Unipersonal (a Spanish company), Research Now S.A.S. (a French Company), Research Now Italy, S.r.l. (an Italian company), Research Now Netherlands B.V. (a Dutch company), Research Now G.K. (a Japanese company), and Research Now India Private Ltd. (an Indian company), together "Research Now", operate the Research Now website. This Privacy Policy governs the website located at www.researchnow.com. 

Research Now is firmly committed to protecting your privacy. Because protecting your privacy is important to us, you may always submit concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or our privacy practices to privacy@researchnow.com. If you choose to write us an e-mail, please reference the Privacy Policy in your subject line. Research Now will attempt to respond to all reasonable concerns and inquiries expeditiously. 

**What do we do?**

Research Now conducts market research in numerous countries around the world using online surveys through the 'Valued Opinions' website and e-Rewards Opinion Panels in relation to existing products and services, advertising campaigns, new product concepts, in fact almost anything. This information is provided in an aggregated and de-identified form to companies all over the world to help them better improve their product or service offerings. 

**Our commitment to protecting your privacy**

We are interested in building a strong, long-lasting relationship with all those who show an interest in our services. When you decide to share your information with us, we feel that it is important to assure you that your information will be safely protected. This statement discloses our information collecting, handling and disclosure practices. 

**How we collect and use your personal information**

We collect personal information from you when you communicate with us by any media. The personal information collected on this website is name, company, title, phone number and email address. We define personal information as any identifiable data relating to a natural person that is directly or indirectly collected, by us or a third party. We collect your personal information on a voluntary basis. If you request a quote or brochure, we may require that you provide specific information to ensure delivery and execution of your request. Any personal information that we collect from the website is passed on to our sales department for follow-up or to provide any information you have requested. 

**Why we collect personal information**

We collect personal information for the following purposes: 

  * to keep you informed and obtain your views of Research Now's products, services and activities; 
  * transferring any personal information to any subsidiary or group company; 
  * statutory and regulatory compliance; 
  * to process any enquiries raised by you and other communications initiated by you in relation to your dealings with Research Now and any services provided by Research Now; 
  * marketing Research Now and its products and services, including those of its group companies and third party suppliers; 
  * when permitted by you, to send you marketing communications keeping you informed about the activities of Research Now; and 
  * achieving the general objectives of Research Now.

**Opt Out**

We do not disclose your personal information to our clients for the purposes of allowing them to conduct direct marketing to you. We may use your personal information ourselves to conduct direct marketing but you are entitled to opt-out from receiving direct marketing communications from us at any time. You may do so by responding to the opt-out option which is included with each direct marketing communication that we send. 

**Permitted Processing**

Research Now ensures that it is permitted to process your personal data. If no statutory condition applies to the form of processing we undertake, we can only undertake such processing with your consent. You may withdraw your consent to our processing your personal data for some of the above purposes by contacting us as privacy@researchnow.com. 

Any personal information you send to us will be treated in the strictest confidence. 

**How we protect your personal information**

Research Now takes reasonable steps to protect your personal information from unauthorised access, use, disclosure or loss. This site has security measures (including on-line and off-line physical, electronic and managerial safeguards) in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information, including your e-mail address, under our control. As with any transmission over the Internet; however, there is always some element of risk involved in sending personal information on-line. Your e-mail address, password and cookie will be required to update your personal information (name, e-mail address, etc.) If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an e-mail to privacy@researchnow.com. 

**Disclosure of your personal information**

We do not pass on personal information to organizations for whom we do market research, whether for research or marketing purposes. Personal information may be shared between members of the group of companies of which Research Now is now a part. 

We do not share, sell, rent or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for their promotional purposes. 

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. 

**Research Now's use of cookies**

We may use technology to track the patterns of behavior of visitors to the site. This can include using a 'cookie', pieces of information that are transferred to an individual user's hard drive for record keeping purposes. At the present time we send a basic cookie to your computer which stores basic information which you enter into the site, which may include your name, address, phone number and email address (Basic Cookies). The Basic Cookie functions by saving your passwords and site preferences. As a result it is possible to speed up your future activities at the site and allow Research Now to provide you with information specifically tailored to your interests. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings. To modify your browser settings click on the help section of your Internet browser and follow the instructions. 

**We are Committed to Children's Privacy**

Research Now takes children’s privacy seriously and we do not seek to collect individually identifiable information about children under 13 years of age. 

If Research Now learns that a child under the age of 13 has submitted personally identifiable information online, in contravention of these measures, Research Now will take all reasonable measures to delete such information from its databases and to not use such information for any purpose. 

**Other Websites**

This Site contains links to other websites. Research Now is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices or the content of any websites which are linked to the Site. 

**How to contact us**

If you have any queries relating to this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at privacy@researchnow.com. 

**Changes to our Privacy Statement**

Please check this page periodically for changes as Research Now reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of the Privacy Policy and the Site at any time. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of any changes to this Policy will mean that you accept such changes. 

If we are going to use personal data in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify the affected individuals by posting a notice on this Site or via email.
